Hillman, Sidney Collection of Correspondence from Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Harry Truman and Related Documents 6219
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Collection of Correspondence from Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Harry Truman and Related Documents
1934-1948
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hillman, Sidney
Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
Truman, Harry
6219
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records, correspondence, memorabilia.
This collection consists of White House memorabilia and correspondence.
6189012
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 04, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of White House memorabilia and correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks
Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1914-1988; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972
6189012
- Roosevelt Era White House Dinner Invitations., 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Roosevelt Era White House. Memorabilia., 1934-1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Roosevelt to Hillman. Correspondence., 1935-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Presidential Inauguration Memorabilia., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Roosevelt Era White House. Reception Invitations., 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Presidential Inauguration Memorabilia., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Federal Building Passes., 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Federal Building Passes. Originals., 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Steven Early to Hillman. Correspondence., 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Public Buildings Administration Passes. Originals., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Presidential Inauguration Memorabilia., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Roosevelt Funeral Services. Announcement., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Truman to Hillman. Correspondence., 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)